GRANT SOLOMON

+1 229.223.6488 \$\phi\$ gsolo2001@outlook.com Portfolio Website—gsolo2001.github.io

PROFILE

I am a dedicated IT professional with B.S. in Computer Science from Valdosta State University.

I have three years of experience working in Valdosta State University's Division of Information Technology as the IT Help Desk's Manager. It was my job to be the liaison between our Division of IT and the rest of the Valdosta State community, to provide them with information, best practices, and training for everything technologically related.

I currently work as the Shop Manager for Event Point, an event production company that focuses on corporate functions. It's my responsibility to manage all our audiovisual equipment, including cataloging, maintenance, and overall upkeep, as well as setting up and running the various events that we produce.

Some of my additional areas of expertise include:

- Web design and development
- Software engineering (both for desktop and mobile platforms)
- Graphic and video production

EDUCATION

B.S. in Computer Science - magna cum laude

May 2022

Valdosta State University - Valdosta, GA

EXPERIENCE

Shop Manager March 2023 - Present

Event Point - Valdosta, GA

- Managing our audiovisual equipment, including cataloging, maintenance, and overall upkeep
- Assist setting up and running the various events that we produce

IT Help Desk Manager

Aug 2021 - March 2023

Valdosta State University - Valdosta, GA

- System Administrator for our work order system (Ivanti Neurons for ITSM)
- Manage the hiring, training, and supervision of our help desk technicians

Web Development Internship

Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

Valdosta State University - Valdosta, GA

- Created a website for the Southwest Georgia Healthcare Partnership
- Learned how to manage and work with clients

IT Help Desk Technician

Feb 2020 - Aug 2021

Valdosta State University - Valdosta, GA

- Tasked with assisting faculty, staff, and students with technology issues
- Provided IT support, knowledge, and training for our help desk agents

PROJECTS

Redesign Ivanti Neurons As System Administrator for Valdosta State University's work order system, I led a project to improve and redesign its end-user experience. I worked on the front and back-end systems to update the application to be professional and end-user focused, and led focus groups to introduce the new design and features.

Agile Software Development. To improve our agile software development skills, I worked with a team to create a Java-based application that allowed you to manage a network of vending machines. The application used GitHub for version control and to organize our tasks and sprints.

Capstone Project. For my capstone project, I worked with a team to create a 2D, retro-style game written in C++. The game engine was coded from scratch, including the physics and rendering, and all the game code was written using object-oriented programming. See my portfolio site (linked at the top) for more information.